screw-paypal.com 2013-04-05

# Screw-PayPal.com Privacy Policy

### _Privacy Policy_

This privacy policy sets out how Screw-Paypal.com and its affiliate sites uses and protects any personal information that you give when you use this website.

We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Screw-Paypal.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. Should any changes be made, the changes will be made to further strengthen the protection of your privacy. This is necessary in order to keep up with rapidly changing internet technology and user habits. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are briefed on what your protections are.

NOTE: This policy is effective as of March 30, 2011. The latest revision of this policy took place on March 30, 2011. Please read this privacy policy carefully. It explains important information about you, your personal information and the privacy of your online activities. 

* * *

_WHAT WE COLLECT_

As soon as you are logged into this site, we collect information about your internet connection, basic system information, and your activities on this site. This information includes your IP address, the web browser you are using, and other basic non identifying information. This information is used for statistical purposes, for improving the content and appearance of this site and for banning those from this site who abuse this site in any way. This collected information will be kept private and will not be shared with anybody. All raw data collected in this fashion is securely deleted after 90 days. 

Should you chose to contact us, or initiate any communication with us, for any purpose, we reserve the right to ask that you submit the following:

  * Name
  * Contact information including email address 
  * Demographic information such as city, postal code, state, and country
  * Other information relevant to your request.

If any personal information is submitted, that information will be kept private. _NO INFORMATION will be given out, sold, rented, or otherwise transmitted_. All outside requests from 3rd parties seeking information on this sites users will be AUTOMATICALLY DENIED. 

NOTE: Exceptions include valid search warrants and court orders from recognized legal and civilized jurisdictions (good luck if you are a court or the police from Iraq or Nigeria). Should this occur, you will be notified by us that your information was given to law enforcement. 

* * *

_WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE GATHER_

If any information about you is volunteered to us, it will be used only in relation to our ongoing struggle to change PayPal’s business practices. Your information could be used for:

  * Developing patterns on where complaints originate from.
  * Compiling statistics.
  * Providing a better service by improving the content of the website.
  * Emailed unsolicited offers and news from Screw-PayPal.com (if you do not wish to receive any unsolicited emails from us, you are free to contact us and make your wishes known -- they will honored).   

* * *

_SECURITY & COOKIES_

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.  

Screw-Paypal.com does send a cookie to your browser for the purpose of monitoring your web surfing habits while on Screw-PayPal.com. This information is used by this site to gather information on the usefulness and popularity of this site's content. This information is only used for site analysis.

The cookie will expire 30 minutes after you leave this site. You may use this site with cookies disabled. See your browser information for instructions on how to disable cookies.

Third Party Advertising:

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

To help support this site, we use Google's Adsense. Please keep in mind, that as a visitor to Screw-PayPal.com, the following applies:

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

If you have further questions or concerns regarding this, or any issue relating to your privacy online while visiting this website, please do not hesitate to contact us! 

* * *

_LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES_

Our website contains links to other websites which we think are relevant, helpful, or entertaining to our visitors. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites. 

These sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. 

If you feel there are improvements or additions that we can make to our Privacy Policy, please do not hesitate to contact us with your suggestion. If your suggestion is valid -- and we are able to comply with it -- we will gladly add it to this portion of our website.
